Guide to the John N. Warfield papers, 1931-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Textual Materials, 1943-2001; (51 boxes)
  - "Saving American Democracy: The Lessons of Three Mile Island," Technology Review Magazine [John G. Kemeny], July 1980 (Box 37, Folder 75)
  - "Citizen Participation Through Communicative Action: Towards A New Synthesis," Lincoln School of Management [Jotin C. Khisty], undated (Box 37, Folder 76)
  - "Better Designs in Half the Time: Implementing Quality Function Deployment," [Bob King], 1989 (Box 37, Folder 77)
  - "Aplicacion de un Sistema Basado ed Conocimiento de Modelacion al Diseno Optimo de Aparatos Electricos," [Jerzy Kowalski], 1997 (Box 37, Folder 78)
  - "Education for Design," [Erich Jantsch], September 1972 (Box 37, Folder 79)
  - "Management Problem Solving & Decision Making," Course Curriculum [Janes F.Ross], undated (Box 37, Folder 80)
  - "Annual Report: City of University," Department of Systems Science, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 81)
  - "Interactive Management Unit Brochures, Description of ISM-PC Used at City University of London," [James F.Ross], undated (Box 37, Folder 82)
  - "Applications of ISM in Planning for a University Department," Systems Prospects & Plenum, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 83)
  - "Using Computer Modeling in the Classroom to Examine Environmental Issues" A Teacher's Guide [Lornia Wallct], July 1978 (Box 37, Folder 84)
  - "Interpretive Structural Modeling," [Kazuhiko Kawamura], undated (Box 37, Folder 85)
  - "Installation of a Computer Aided Problem Solving System at Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation," Christakis & Associates Draft Proposal [Alexander N. Christakis], March 15, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - "General Professional Correspondence," Letters About I.S.M., undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - "Winnebago Tribe of Nebraska," Correspondence, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - "Council for Scientific & Inudstrial Research," Correspondence with Moses B. Ayiku, 1975-1978 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - "Correspondence with Keeneth Butler,", 1977 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - "Correspondence with Norman Cousins, Chairman Editorial Board of Saturday Review", 1980 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - "Correspondence Related to Appointment of George J. Klir as Distinguished Professor at S.U.N.Y," New York, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - "Correspondence with Wiley & Son's, Review of George Klir - Pergamon Encyclopedia", 1984 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - "Principles of Design & Appraisal of Statistical Information Systems," Correspondence Related to (I.S.M.) [David Rosenblatt], 1980 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - "Correspondence with Will Thissen, Department of Information Systems," Netherlands, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - "Correspondence with Donald V.Steward, Computer Science Department, California, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - "Correspondence with Hanny Nurmi, Department of Political Sciences, Finland", 1977 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - "Correspondence with Ebasco Services, Bill Livingstone", undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - "International Federation for Systems Research (I.F.S.R.) Newsletter, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - "General de Sistemas Y Cibernetica, Newsletter & Academy in Problems", 1987 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - "International Federation for Systems Research," Draft & Other Correspondence [John N. Warfield], 1987 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - "Boletin Sistemas Generales (S.E.S.G.E), Promoteres Del Desarrollo," Madrid, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - "Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R), Correspondence", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - "Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R), Minutes, Teleconferencing,Schedules & Agenda of Meetings", 1983 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - "Correspondence with J. F.Welch, General Electric Company", 1990 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - "International Society for the Systems Sciences" General Systems Bulletin, 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - "International Society for the Systems Sciences," General Systems Bulletin, 1975-1982 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - "Carnage Mellon University Correspondence with Joel A.Tarr, Associate Dean, College of Humanities & Social ScienceS, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - "The Systemist,United Kingdom Systems Society", 1988 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - "Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R), Membership Lists", 1977 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - "Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R), Membership List ", 1984 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - "National Science Foundation (N.S. F), Proposal Review", 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - "National Science Foundation (N.S. F), Proposal Evaluation Forms", 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - "American Association for the Advancement of Science (A.A.A.S) & Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R) Correspondence", 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - "American Management Association Membership Card Information," [John N. Warfield], 1981 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - "Institute of Electrical & Electronic Engineers (I.E.E.E) Directory of Officers & Committee Chairman," Correspondence, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - >"Communications & the Future," The Fourth General Assembly of World Future Society, July 22, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - "Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R) Conference Call", undated (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - "Joint National Meeting," Call for Papers, undated (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - "Texas A & M University Correspondence with August W.Smith," Related to ( S.G.S.R), 1982 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - "International Correspondence Between 1982-1992" (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - "Correspondence with National Science Foundation (N.S. F) Regarding Joint Symposium of (S.G.S.R) & (A.A.A.S), July 27, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - "Call for Symposium Proposals, Detroit Meeting,"Joint Session: (S.G.S.R) & (A.A.A.S), May 27, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - "Update on Meeting Arrangements for Twenty Seventh Annual Meeting of (S.G.S.R), in Detroit", December 1982 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - "First Draft Concept for a Theme, Detroit Meeting of (S.G.S.R)", December 1982 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - "Curriculum Vitae From Who's Who in America," Deutsch Karl Wolfgang, undated (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - "Internal Affairs Committee, Society for General Research (S.G.S.R)", January 1982 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - "General Systems Bulletin, Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R)," Fall Volumes, 1981-1983 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - "General Systems Bulletin, Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R)," Winter Volumes, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - "General Systems Bulletin, Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R)," Spring - Summer Volumes, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - "General Systems Bulletin, Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R)," Fall Volumes, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - "General Systems Bulletin, Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R)," Summer Volumes, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - "Society for General Systems Research (S.G.S.R) Yearbook & Index ,", 1956-1971 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - "Cosmos Club Proposal from for Membership, Associate Privileges", April 6, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - "Far West Laboratory, Report on Fuschl Symposium," Correspondence with Bela H.Banathy], 1983 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - "The Fuschl Conversations 1982," Proceedings, Mary 9, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - "Structural Thinking & Interactive Management," Short Course in Fall 1994, June 10, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - "Seminar: Complexity in Organizations," 1999 Spring Semester Class, February 27, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - "The Institute of Public Policy (T.I.P.P) Course: PUB 710 Managing Organizational Complexities, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - "Structure Based Theory of Complexity & Some Applications," Colloquium-97 (T.I.P.P), April 24, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - "The Institute of Public Policy (T.I.P.P) Course - PUB 833," SPRING, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - "Forty- Three Authors Illustrate Non-Integrative Communication Concerning the Japanese Miracle," [Michael F. Litzelman], September 28, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - "Social System Design Course at University of Northern Iowa," Spring, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - "Social Systems Design Problems," [John N. Warfield], September 1980 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - "Social Systems Design -Systems 781 Course Outline & Syllabus," University of Virginia, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - "Study Questions for a Science of Generic Design," (D.S.M.C. Class), August 1990 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - "Study Question for Peter Senges's Book: The Fifth Discipline," Fall, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - "An Example of an Options Field," Handouts (D.S.M.C. Class), 1987 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - "Example of an Options Profile," Classroom Handouts, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - "An Example of a Delta Chart," Classroom Handouts, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - "Course - Engineering 250, Handouts Spiral Bound Book," University of Virginia, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - "Student Design Reports for Engineering Course- 250 Class," University of Virginia, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - "Conflict Resolution Course 623," Class Roster & Grade List, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - "Generic Design Course Proposal & Outline - UNIV 431," Fall Semester, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - "Social Systems Design Course Proposal at George Mason University," [John N. Warfield], 1987 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - "Communication Course - COMM 399, Study Questions & Handouts," Fall Semester, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - "Communications Course - COMM 531, Application to Facilitating Group Communication," Course Outline, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - "Communications Course - COMM 399, List of Case Studies,Notesbooks& Course Syllabus," Fall, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - "A Review of the Fifth Discipline: A Concept, Not a Plan," Term Paper [Sharon Heidtman], July 1991 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - "Electronic Meeting Systems to Support Group Work," received From Sharon Heidtman, July 25, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - "The Application of General Systems Theory Based Concepts to an Organizational Analysis," [Sharon Heidtnan], July 25, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - "The Defense Systems Management College (D.S.M.C), A Learning Organization ?," Term Paper for PUAD -796 Course [George Tony Perino], 1991 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - "Student Term Papers for the Course PUAD 729, Public Administration Course," George Mason University, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - "Student Term Papers for Course PUAD 729, Report on Peter Senge's Book," George Mason University, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - "Course Material for Public Administration 729," Students Resumes, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - "Curriculum Proposal for Defense Systems Management College (D.S.M.C.)," Three Year Program Overview, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - "Defense Systems Management College (D.S.M.C) Class Members, Degree Interests," Fort Belvior -VA, undated (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - "Defense Systems Management College (D.S.M.C) Faculty Degree Interests," Fort Belvior -VA, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - "Correspondence Regarding D.S.M.C) Class Credit in PUAD 729 ", 1991 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - "Public Administration Course PUAD 729, Students Resumes, Syllabus, Course Outlines," George Mason University, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - "Institute of Advanced Study in Integrative Studies (IASIS ) & Center for Interactive Management (CIM) Internal Correspondence & Projects", undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - "International Intersystems Services, Correspondence with the Publishers", 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - "Societal Systems Correspondence Letters", 1988 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - "Book Inventory List -Warfield Collection of Book", undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - "Correspondence with Pat TrusellL, Regarding 1990 ISSS Meeting in Portland", undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - "Workshops on System Engineering for Indian Scientists & Engineers, Correspondence & Projects", 1978 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - "TATA Management Training Center & I.E.E.E Bombay Correspondence Regarding Systems Approach in India", 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - "Various Correspondents Addresses & Business Cards During India Trip, Regarding (I.S.M), 1979 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - "Phased Program for (Genesys, U.P.P) & (I.S.M .) in India Proposal," Correspondence with G.S.Chandy, February 23, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - "Comparison Works of Sage & Kawamura," Correspondence, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - "Chronology File, Internal Affairs Correspondence", 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - "Nexus - The Newsletter of the Center for Interactive Management," A Collection of Past Issues: 1982-1987 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - "American Institute of Interactive Management (A.I.I.M) Correspondence", June 18, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - "Research Organizations in West Germany," Center for Interactive Management Report, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - "Preparation of Templates, Mailing Labels,Business Cards, Memo Labels", 1984 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - "Consideration for Transferring Technologies & Brazil's Experience in Transferring Microelectronic Technology," Draft Paper India Trip, March 24, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - "Consensus Methodologies," [John N. Warfield], September 1982 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - "Seminar Schedules, Genesys Consultants Correspondence, India Travel", 1983 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - "Projects & Conferences, Seminars in India," Correspondence About Systems Engineering, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - "England - Projects & Correspondence About ( I.S.M), undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - "China - Projects & Correspondence About System Research, undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - "Estudios Economicos - Prjectt & Correspondence Material with Ecuador", 1988 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - "Gahna - Transfer Technology Center (T.T.C) Correspondence", 1988-1990 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - "General Correspondence Related to Hiring Policies & Procedures for International Faculty", 1988 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - "October 1983 Visit to Fraunhofer Gesellschaft,West Germany," a Report [J.E.Gibson], November 1983 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - "October 1983 Visit to Fraunhofer Gesellschaft,West Germany," a Report Volume 1 & 2[J.E.Gibson], November 1983 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - "An Analysis of West Germany Design & Manufacturing Productivity - Visit to Fraunhofer Gesellschaft", November 1985 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - "Proposal for Establishment of a Center for Research on Artificial Intelligence (A.I)," [Kenneth de Jong, Henry Hamburger], April 27, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - "Center for Interactive Management (C.I.M) Internal Correspondence & Grants, Projects," IASIS - George Mason University, 197-1989 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - "The Ecosystems Project- An Approach to Environmental Management," Genesys Consultants, India, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - "Towards a Credo for the Management of Environment," Genesys Consultants India[G.S.Chandy], 1984 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - "Seminar Ideas in India," Schedules & Plans, 1981-1984 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - "University Day, George Mason University, April 6, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - "Various Correspondence with Poland About System Research", undated (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - "Projects & Correspondence with Spain About Systems Research", undated (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - "Argentina General Systems & Cybernetics - Newsletter," Other Related Correspondents, November 1988 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - "Mexico - Projects & Conferences & Correspondence Material", undated (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - "Projects, Conferences & Correspondences - Japan", undated (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - "Projects, Conferences & Correspondences - Hungary", undated (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - "Projects, Conferences & Correspondences - Brazil", undated (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - "Projects, Conferences & Correspondence - Italy", undated (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - "Projects, Conferences & Correspondences - France", undated (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - "Projects, Conferences & Correspondences - Switzerland", undated (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - "Correspondence with Giorgio Tonella,", undated (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - "Systems Research Correspondence with Dr.Klaus Kornwachs", undated (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - "Pan -Earth Project, Venezuela Case Study", 1989 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - "Projects, Conferences & Correspondences - International", undated (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - "Product Information Management Strategy," Ford Motor Company, May 1994 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - "Short Course Plans -Ford Motor Company", 1998 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - "Powertrain Control Systems, Draft," Ford Motor Company, July 1996 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - "Ford Symposium - Design Theory & Methodology," Ford Motor Company, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - "Design Theory - Symposium, Correspondence with Scott Staley," Ford Motor Company, 1989-1991 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - "National Center for Manufacturing Sciences (N.C.M.S), Correspondence & Activities,", 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - "End User Access Project & Correspondence," Scott Staley of Ford Motor Company, February 1991 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - "Copyright Release on InteractivE Management Handbook Given to Ford Motor Company & Defense System Management College", February 1992 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - "Ford Plan for Analytical Powertrian Workshops", February 1992 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - "Ford Chronology Notebook" [John N. Warfield], March 1992 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - "Literature Relevant to Evolution of Quality Function Deployment," Ford Motor Company, July 18, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - "Ford Science Center Idea for Eastern Europe," ( F.M.C), July 1992 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - "I.E.E.E Spectrum, Concurrent Engineering", July 1991 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - "Engineering World, Newsletter", May 1992 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - "Analytical Powertrain: Development of an Integrated CAD/CAM/CAE System," Presentation, January 23, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - "Process Improvement, a Guide for Management", 1992 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - "Steps to Improve Process - Ford P.I.P (Process Improvement Plan), December 1991 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - "Language Issues in Design of Crankshaft Process Improvement Plan," Ford Motor Company, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - "The Design Research Institute in Cornell Campus," Ford Motor Company, March 1991 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - "Total Quality Management Brochure: Ten Elements for Implementation, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - "Research Staff & Business Plan - Ford Motor Company", 1991 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - "Options Profile Data& Cultural Problems - Ford Workshop", September 23, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - "The 36 Highest Priority Long Term Cultural Options," Table R-2, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - "Lowering Cultural Barriers to Analytical Powertrain," Draft [Robert Delosh], November 1991 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - "Science of Cultural Change in Organizations," Staley, Scott Proposal, September 1, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop #4, & Other Correspondence", 1992 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop # 3, & Other Correspondence", 1992 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop #2, & Other Correspondence", 1992 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop #1, & Other Correspondence", 1992 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - "Analytical Powertrain Workshop #1, & Other Correspondence", 1992 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - "Application of Interactive Management to System Wide Planning for Analytical Powertrain," Proposal to Ford Motor Company, May 1992 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - "Interactive Management Sessions for Ford Motor Company," Vax Files Set up by Benjamin Broome, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - "Planning for ( A.P.T) Workshops for Ford Motor Company", 1992 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - "Ford Motor Company People List - Names,Job Titles & Department Affiliation", April 1992 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - "Replies by Members of the Information Technology Research Council," [John N. Warfield], February 1985 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - "Information Technology Research Council (I.T.R.C) First Meeting"Membership Lists, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - "A Proposal for Locating the Technology Transfer Study Center at the Institute for Information Technology (I.I.T)," Prepared for John N. Warfield [David S. Bushnell], September 9, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - "A Report to the Vice President for Academic Affairs on the Status & Future of the International Programs," International Programs Advisory Committee( I.P.A.C), 1986 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - "David J.King's Research, Patent, Copyright & Space Policies," George Mason University, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - "David J.King's Policies & Committee, Proposals & Correspondences," George Mason University, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - "Space Research Center Committee," at George Mason University, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - "Super Computer Usage Committee," George Mason University Collaboration with Colorado State University, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - "Computer Based Education Consortium Idea," Report, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - "Computer Based Education - Reports & Graphical Chart", 1985 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - "Computer Based Education - Reports & Graphical Chart", 1985 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - "Structural Thinking: Producing Effective Organizational Change," [John N. Warfield], 1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - "Accelerating Productivity of Intellectual Organizations by Systems Methodologies," Japan Symposium,Japan, November 1994 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - "Accelerating Productivity of Intellectual Organizations by System Methodologies," Seminar Talk at Mexico, October 1994 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - "Interpretive Structural Modeling PC Software User's Guide", December 1990 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - "The Institute of Public Policy (T.I.P.P) Internal Affairs Proposals, Contracts & Correspondences," George Mason University, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - "The Institute of Public Policy (T.I.P.P) Internal Affairs Proposals, Contracts & Correspondences," George Mason University, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - "Learning Organization," Listserve, Webpage Information, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - "Learning Organization," Warfield's Correspondence", 1995 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - "Learning Organization," Warfield's Correspondence", 1996 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - The Great University, Meeting with the Provost," At George Mason University, 1986-1988 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - "The Great University - Agenda, Meetings & Ideas", undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - "Innovative Research Advisory Committee, Agenda," Presentation of Annual Report, June 1986 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - "Faculty Advisory Group for Institute for Information Technology (I.I.T)," Proposal's, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - "Generic Design Course Offering in 1985," A Report (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - "Advertisement for Computer & Information Systems Department Chair," George Mason University, November 5, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - "Academic Computing Advisory Committee (A.C.A.C), Announcements, Meetings Agenda & Proposal's," George Mason University, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - "Center for Innovative Technology (C.I.T) Plans & Proposal's", 1986 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Averett Tombes, Entrepreneurship Programs & Proposal's& Committee Discussions", 1986 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - "Averett Tombes, Entrepreneurship Programs & Proposal's & Research Advisory Committee", 1986 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - "Averttt Tombes,Operational Policies & Proposal's", 1986 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - "George Mason University Task Force on Computer Aided Instruction," Report, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - "Computer Baaed Education, Learning -George Mason University Task Force," Articles, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - "Research Planning Center at George Mason University, Character Recognition & Information Technology", 1986 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - "Research Planning Center at George Mason University, Center for Interactive Management, Management of Software Productivity Center,Research Leader Program", 1986 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - "Meeting's with Dr. King to Report on Institute for Information Technology Activities," George Mason University, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - "Planning for Research Center's at George Mason University, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 15)